I never would have thought...
I can't believe the CLI can create such a flexible, limitless canvas.
So, Jimeng AI's CLI has been out for a little while now.
But a lot of people aren't quite sure what it can actually do.
But actually, it's capable of a whole lot.
So today, I'm going to show you an infinite canvas based on the Jimeng CLI.
I call it the 'web workflow'.
So, first off, let's see... he kinda looks like Combi.
The UI nodes can be freely combined.
All of Dreamina's full-power models are right here.
For example, this is the image model, and you can select 5.0 from it.
4.0,
The entire series supports 2K and 4K resolutions, and this one is the video model.
For video generation, you can upload up to nine reference images.
For the three video references, the C-Down model is the full-power version 2.0.
So basically, it's got everything you could possibly need.
And of course, this is also linked to your own Dreamina account.
So, let's click on this spot right here.
And as you can see, your login information is right here.
your Dreamina credits
This is completely synced with your own Dreamina account.
So, you don't need to deal with any extra API-related operations.
So it has nothing to do with APIs at all.
Alright, let's open up a new window.
So, this is what the initial canvas looks like.
So, our main focus here is on the canvas.
Normally, you'd have to add some nodes.
None of this is particularly difficult.
But doing it that way is a real hassle.
But let's focus on this section over here on the right.
And it's connected to Doubao.
This is an agent.
So, right here, we can generate nodes through a conversational interface.
So, for example, let's start by generating an image.
We'll just tell it to generate an image.
The content should be a cat.
So, it's calling Doubao to create a workflow for us.
It's incredibly smart.
So, the entire process of setting up all these nodes,
We don't have to do any of that manually.
Okay, so the workflow for generating a cat is all set.
We just click on it, and it'll load right onto the canvas.
Alright, it's pretty much the same as the last one.
And right here, we can go ahead and select the model.
Let's go with 4.6.
So it's just a cat.
Let's hit 'Generate'.
So, after a moment,
And the cat picture will pop up right inside this node.
Alright, the cat image is done.
This is the simplest way to do it.
Alright, let's crank up the difficulty now.
So, right after telling it to generate a cat picture,
and we need to make it move.
And just like that.
And then, let's load it in.
So now, as you can see, besides the node for drawing the cat,
And then, a new node was added for generating a video from the image.
And just like that, we can also select the video model version right here.
Let's go with C-down 1.2.0.
And then, let's make an eight-second video. Alright.
Alright, so the first step is to generate this cat.
We'll go with a more recent model.
Generate it with 4.6.1.
And this is the exact same process as before.
Alright, so the image generation node is now running.
Once it's done, we can then generate a video.
Once we have this cat image ready,
So, right here, we'll just click on 'Generate Video'.
While we're waiting,
We can open up the cat that Dreamina just generated.
And this feature is also available right inside the Dreamina chat box.
The video is being generated.
It should be ready in a moment.
Alright, let's head back to the canvas.
And there's the video of the cat, it's back.
We can click here to play it.
An eight-second video of a really cute cat.
It's using the c-down 1.2.0 model.
And this video is also available in your own Dreamina account.
But of course, this canvas can do so much more.
It also supports multimodal inputs.
We can upload images for it right here.
Alright, let's refresh the page.
Let's try that again.
Let's open up this chat.
Let's just toss a few images at it.
and tell it about these two characters.
Generate a promotional still of these two characters on a stand-up comedy stage.
And send it off.
And then, it will use these two images to create a workflow.
Let's click on it.
And as you can see, the two images are already in here.
All we need to do is just click 'Create'.
So, we'll use these two characters as our reference.
and it will generate a scene of them on stage.
Alright, the dual-image mode has been generated.
And of course, after that, we can connect a video node.
We've already demonstrated this in the first example.
This lets you create a continuous video sequence.
And you can even extend the video.
So, to quickly recap the CLI...
Basically, it acts as a bridge.
any of our AI platforms or services,
and connect to any platform through the CLI.
For example, this local canvas we're building from scratch right now.
So, next time, I'll show you all how to build this Web Workflow canvas from scratch.
I'm a PhD student.
See you next time. Bye!